VISHNUS

+91- 90801 97960 | vishnuskalai21@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio

Career Objective

To land a challenging job in a reputable company so I may broaden my knowledge, skills, and learnings. Obtain a responsible career path that will allow me to make the most of my education and experience while significantly contributing to the organization's growth.

Experience

Smartinternz, Telangana

Dec 2023 - Feb 2024

Software Test Automation

- I Successfully completed a comprehensive software test automation internship, gaining hands-on experience in automating test cases using Katalon Studio.
- Developed proficiency in creating and executing automated test scripts for Amazon and Cura Healthcare to ensure software quality and efficiency.

Gyanmatrix, Coimbatore

Oct 2024 - Present

QA Intern

- I actively contribute to an Agile development process by writing test cases, identifying bugs, and performing cross-browser and cross-platform testing.
- Perform manual testing on the Digri web application, gaining hands-on experience to ensure high-quality software delivery.

Projects

Collaborative Content Creation Platform | HTML, CSS, Git

• This platform is used to create new content, edit existing content, send reports to creators, access the admin page, add new creators with admin privileges, and share content with others.

Test Automation Using Katalon Studio | Katalon Studio, Excel, Jenkins

• Test all website functionalities using Katalon Studio. Create plans, test cases, test suites, test suite collections, perform cross-browser testing, and execute command-line testing and ect.

Files Arrangement | Python, Git

 This Python script organizes files into different directories based on their types. It creates separate folders for images, music, videos, executables, archives, torrents, documents, code files, and design files.

Technical Skills

Languages: Python, SQL, HTML/CSS, OOPS

Frameworks: Selenium

Software Testing: Manual Testing, Automation Testing, Jira, Jenkins, CI/CD

Developer Tools: Git, GitHub, VS Code, Debugging

Operating Systems: Linux, Windows

Education

CMS College of Science and Commerce

Coimbatore,

Post-Graduation in Master of Computer Application

Aug 2022 - April 2024

CMS College of Science and Commerce

Coimbatore.

Graduation in Information Technology

June 2019 - May 2022

Accomplishment

I participated in the Department-level hackathon program in 2023 and won second place.